Ajay,
senior citizens
constitute almost one percent of our country's population. Due to this, the
biggest
impact on hospitalization expenses has
fallen on senior citizens.
In this environment, a
mediclaim policy becomes very important for senior citizens.
[Music]
Medical costs always keep coming up. Therefore,
before taking a CSA policy, if possible,
take a longer term policy.
What will happen by this is that the future expenses will
also be covered. There is a surcharge
in the Srijan policy as well,
that means if the copay is 20%, then if the
bill comes for Rs. 1 lakh, then the customer will have to pay 40%. If we
compare the remaining 8%, then Rs. 1
lakh, then in this the customer has to pay Rs. 20,000
and the company will offer Rs. 80,000.
Before taking a senior citizen policy, it becomes
very important to look at the copy.
Apart from this, some other checks should be done, some
other points should be considered like
what is its waiting period,
after how many years it will become active, whether there is a
medical checkup or not.  It is also
important for us to see how much
percentage is there, many companies also charge 14%, saying
that the team needs to operate, so
we see all this in a chart, for all
your lovers, we have done the calculations on this for a seventy
year old as of today's
date, let us know that at the
time of riots, it
is very important for senior citizens to have a minimum deposit of Rs 5 lakh, if
you can afford it, then you can
also take a combination of it, if there is any
problem in taking finance, then you can do this, let's say Rs 3
lakh and with it a policy of one and a half,
this will reduce the traffic, this is a cumin,
many companies offer specific policies for citizens
like Pista, New India Assurance,
Bajaj Allianz, HDFC Ergo etc.
But before doing anything, it is
important to see that it creates its meeting,
along with the distinguished time given in it,
for this, how much is the cover, this
second cost, this is also important to see once, so
these are many aspects which
we should first be familiar with,
after that  You should select only that, then where is the
senior citizen, there is a
senior citizen policy available in the market
and there is a regular quality one, so it is
better
that if you can do this then it is
better to take a regular policy because there is no co-payment in it
and it has some extra
features like there is no compulsion of some charges which
can be folded, so
take a regular policy, if you cannot do this then it is
better for a senior citizen to take a better quality than this,
which is the best quality for a senior citizen, according to me,
if there are two factors in this, if the
subscriber is above 65 then
this subscription, which
almost all the companies have
competition of specific charges in a healthy manner, all
other expenses will be covered, bank
charges maximum normal water, district
or any higher which is Rs.1000, you will
not get more than this, subscribe,
due to which all the expenses will be covered,
but if the subscriber is above 65 years of age,
which is a subscription for senior citizens, then a
little bit we  People can give copies
but the expenses will be borne by Meghdootam, so
my friends, if you
want a customized product and prominent
services along with it, then
my contact details are given in the description box, you
can contact them on
that I will adversely affect your opinion,
thank you friends, thank you